麦琪∶已经连续5天了.
Maggie: That's five days in a row.
杰森∶今天早上又没有报纸!
Jason: No paper again this morning!
杰森∶更重要的是,我下个月一定要从帐单里面扣除2美元.
Jason: And more importantly that's two Dollars I'm deducting from next months bill
麦琪∶啊?没有利息吗?
Maggie: What, no interest?
杰森∶对,2美元14分.
Jason: Two Dollars and fourteen Cents.
麦琪∶你在给谁打电话?
Maggie: Who are you calling?
杰森∶劳驾,这并不是针对你个人,
Jason: Excuse me, this isn't directed at you personally,
只是想知道你们的投递员是怎么回事?已经有连续5天没有送报纸过来了!!
but what the hell of two bit newspaper are you people running down there?
我已经检查过灌木..屋顶.
Five mornings in a row there's nothing in my driveway!!
不,我们没有泳池.
Yes, I checked the bushes...yes the roof.No, we don't have a pool.
你不能让我等!我希望你们能马上处理这件事!
No you can't put me on hold!I want this taken care of right away!
我要求扣除2美元14分.14分是利息.
I want a rebate for two Dollars fourteen Cents.It's interest.Hello.
哈罗,他让我等.
He put me on hold.
麦琪∶不能说的好像我们家支付不起游泳池一样,知道吗?
Maggie: It's not like we couldn't afford a pool, you know?
杰森∶我是,我的地址是:罗宾汉15巷.好,
Jason: Oh, yes, yes, my address; fifteen Robin Hood Lane.
我很愿意直接跟送报纸的家伙谈,他的号码是多少?
Oh, yes, I would love to talk to the paper boy directly.What's his number?
不要跟我绕圈子,这是我自己的号码!这个报童叫什么名字?
Don't run your mind games on me, that's my number!What's this bozo's name?
报刊经销商∶迈克尔,在宁静的早晨,
Newsagent: Michael, how's my fledgling paper boy doing,
我的新报童做的怎么样?
this fine pristine morning?
迈克∶嗨!菲莉.你好吗?
Mike: Hey, OK Philly.How you doing?
菲莉∶哦!满意极了.
Philly: Oh, quite satisfactorily.
再次提醒你,要执行我提出的神圣的命令.
But then again, carrying out the sacred mandated first amendment is
my raison d'etre
迈克∶嗨!嗨!你说了我刚刚想说的话.
Mike: Hey, hey, you took the words right out of my mouth.
菲莉∶给你.
Philly: Here you go.
迈克∶谢谢.
Mike: Alright.Thanks.
菲莉∶不要马上取出.
Philly: Don't exhume just yet.
迈克∶我怎么会呢?我还没有喝咖啡呢.
Mike: Hey, how could I?I haven't had my coffee.
等一下,
Wait a minute, Philly,
菲莉,我以为我只要递送200份报纸就够了.
I thought I was only supposed to deliver two hundred papers.
菲莉∶是200份.
Philly: Exactamundo.
迈克:菲莉,两百份报纸可不是这个样子的.
Mike: Ah, but...ah...Philly, two hundred papers didn't look like this, all last week
菲莉∶周末版,迈克尔.
Philly: Sunday edition, Michael.
托尼∶真地?
Mike: Really?
菲莉∶难道你认为所有的报纸都像星期一那么简单吗?
Philly: You think that it's merely capricious that we initiate paper carriers
不可能的!
on Monday?Nay, nay!
杰森:迈克.
Jason: Mike.
迈克∶嗨!爸爸.
Mike: Hey, Dad.
杰森∶你找到了工作也不跟我们说一声.
Jason: You got a job!You didn't tell us.
迈克∶爸爸,每次我跟你们说我做了点负责的事情,
Mike: Dad, I mean,
你们都会用怀疑的目光看着我,然后呢,
every time I tell you that I've done something responsible,
就会很兴奋,
you always give me that look, and you get so excited and you say,
就会说:我的乖宝宝!我只是不想你们又这样对我.
that's my boy!I'm just trying to avoid that.
杰森∶知道了!那我们整个星期的报纸都到哪里去了?
Jason: Done!Where's my stinking paper been all week?
迈克∶在楼上我的房间呢,爸爸;那可是我递送的第一份报纸!
Mike: It's right up in my place, Dad; it's the first one that I deliver!
杰森∶那些都是我的报纸;你欠我2美元.
Jason: Yeah, well those are my papers, you owe my two Dollars.
迈克∶啊?没有利息吗?
Mike: What, no interest?
杰森:真是太打击人了.
Jason: That hurts, Mike that really hurts.
迈克∶爸爸,我...
Mike: Dad, I...
杰森∶我知道!我知道!你有报纸要送!你找到工作了!啊唷!!
Jason: I know!I know!You got papers to deliver!You got a job!Ow!Go!
去!去吧!我的孩子!嗨!我那该死的报纸呢?
Go!That's my boy!Hey, where's my stinking paper?
迈克∶哦!我累死了!你猜猜我今天送了多少份报纸?
Mike: Oh, I am exhausted!Guess how many papers I delivered today?
开萝尔∶一份.
Carol: One.
迈克∶不,200!
Mike: No, two hundred!Two O O!And we're talking Sunday papers here, Carol.
2个0哦!开萝尔,
We're talking huge, mountainous, heavy papers.
并且我们说的是庞大的,如山的,
This is the hardest fifty Bucks I've ever made!
大量的星期日版.
You know, I think I was tricked.
这是我赚到的最难的 50元!我感觉自己被骗了.
Fifty Dollars a day is fine when there's no news,
没有什么新闻的时候,50美元一天还不错,
but what's with theseworld leaders?I mean...
世界上的领导者都是怎么回事?他们为什么要等到周末来滔滔不绝地讲话呢?
why do these world leaders wait until the weekend to spout off?
开萝尔∶迈克,如果我现在离开房间,
Carol: Mike, it might look like I'm leaving the room right now because
可能看起来像是因为我不愿意听你自怜的唠叨;但是不是那样的!
I don't care to listen to your self-pitying babble; but that's not the case!
而是因为你悲伤的经历让我如此感动,
I'm just so moved by your sad story that I have to go to another room
因此,我不得不到另一个房间去流泪.
and weep.
迈克∶非常感谢,开萝尔.
Mike: Thanks a lot, Carol.
开萝尔∶迈克,我不是傻瓜!我知道你是怎么想的.
Carol: Mike, I'm not a fool!I know what you're thinking.
迈克∶你知道?
Mike: You do?
开萝尔∶当然,首先悲伤的经历,
Carol: Alright, first the sad story,
然后提及到我不可能忽视的50美元,
then the mention of fifty Dollars I couldn't miss it, and the coup de grace,
但是致命一击是,你承认自己不能处理这个工作.
your admission that you couldn't handle the job.
迈克∶那我可以怎么来理解你的话?
Mike: So, what do I think this means?
开萝尔∶还不明显吗?
Carol: Isn't it obvious?
迈克∶当然,对我!
Mike: Err...well yeah, of course, to me!
我只是想要看看你能不能明白.
But I just wanna see how close you can come.
开萝尔∶你希望我接过报纸递送的工作!然后呢,
Carol: You want me to take over your paper round!
用少的可怜的50美元一天的报酬来打发我,而你自己就赚剩余的真实报酬.
And pay me a measly fifty dollars a day while you keep the rest of what
这个对我来说没用的,
you're really paid.Well it won't work, deliver your own stinking papers,
快去递送你那该死的报纸吧.2个0的!
all two O O of them.
迈克∶开萝尔,你在胡说!
Mike: Well you're nuts, Carol!Really nuts!
真的胡说!我可从来没有这么无耻的想法.但是现在就有了……
It never occurred to me to skim off the top.But now that it does...
开萝尔∶迈克,当一个人想要对别人耍诡计的时候,
Carol: When one runs a scam, Mike,
应该找个比自己愚蠢的人,如果他可以找得到的话.
one should pray on one dumber than oneself, if one can find one.
本∶早上好迈克.
Ben: Morning Mike.
迈克∶嗨!;早上好本,本 .嗨!
Mike: Hey, morning Ben.Ben.Hey, hey, hey, how is one?I mean...err...
嗨!嗨!一个人怎么样?我是说今天早上怎么样?
how are you this morning?
本∶哈?
Ben: Ha?
开萝尔∶嗨!本,我不是傻瓜!我知道你是怎么想的.
Mike: Hey Benny, I'm not stupid, I know what you're thinking.
本∶想什么?
Ben: What?
迈克∶你一定在想对于送报纸这样的事,
Mike: You're thinking that with this paper round thing,
他们一定在浪费钱!我作为你的哥哥,
they're practically giving money away!
应该要和你一起分享这笔财富.
And as I as your bro, should share the wealth.
本∶哪,事实上我正在想穿着比基尼的劳拉-林.
Ben: Na, actually I was thinking of Laura-Lynn in a bikini.
迈克∶难道她不会被一个每天可以挣25美元的家伙感动吗?
Mike: And wouldn't she be impressed with a guy who's pulling down twenty
five Bucks a day?
本∶事实上她根本不穿比基尼.
Ben: Actually she wasn't wearing a bikini.
迈克∶本,本,
Mike: Ben!Benny, come on, you're not listening to me;
你根本没听我在说什么,我要把我报纸一办的报酬送给你!
I am offering you half of my paper route!
本∶你有送报纸报酬!
Ben: You have a paper route!
迈克∶是.
Mike: Yes.
本∶你要给我一半?
Ben: And you're giving me half of it?
迈克∶是的,仅仅200份报纸,一天25元.
Mike: Yes, a mere two hundred papers, and that's twenty five Bucks a day.
本∶嗨!太好了!
Ben: Hey, this is great!
迈克∶等等,
Mike: Oh oh, wait a second, Ben;
本;妈妈和爸爸决不会让你在这个年纪工作的.
Mom and Dad are never gonna let you have a job at your age.
本:好的,我不说出去.
Ben: Well, I won't tell 'em.
迈克,咱俩好,别说.
Oh, come on, Mike, be a pal and don't tell either.
迈克∶好,知道了.但是记住,你欠我一个人情.
Mike: Well, OK.But remember, you owe me.
迈克∶再见.
Mike: See ya.
本∶25元一天,根本不划算!
Ben: Twenty five Bucks a day, it aint worth it!
加里∶嗨!本,怎么样?
Gary: Hey Benny, how's it going?
本∶在我的衣服没干前,我哪里也不能去.
Ben: It's not going anywhere until it dries out.
加里∶你上课要迟到了.
Gary: You're gonna be late for school.
本:加里,你不想做一个报童,
Ben: Gary, you don't have any idea what it's like to be a paper boy,
是么?
do you?
加里∶骑一辆自行车,扔几份报纸,就可以赚大钱了.
Gary: Ride a bike, throw a few papers, make big Bucks.
本∶哈.但是你会全身湿透.
Ben: Ha.But you get wet.
加里∶嗨!如果你不想做,我愿意做.
Gary: Hey, if you don't want to do it, I'd do it.
报酬多少?5元?10元?
I mean what's it pay?Five Bucks?Ten Bucks?
本:十元.我挣十元.好的,加里,你帮我做吧.
Ben: Ten Bucks!I get...ten Bucks.OK, Gary, you can have my paper route.
加里∶等一下,你为什么放弃所有的钱?
Gary: Wait a minute, why are you giving up all this money?
本∶啊,是个人原因.
Ben: Ah, it's kind of personal.
托尼∶真地?
Gary: Really?
本∶医疗原因.骑车太多,
Ben: Medical reasons.Well from riding my bike so much,
对报童的胯部不好.
I got paper boy's crotch.Ooh...
如果你不得不像这样走的话,
All the money in the world isn't worth anything,
那世界上的钱还有什么用.那我们说定了?
if you have to walk like this.So we got a deal?
加里∶好!让我们不要动摇.
Gary: Yeah!Let's not shake on it.
本∶不必担心,我不会的.
Ben: Don't worry, I hear it too.
麦琪∶不,不,
Maggie: No, no, I am not a subscriber with a complaint; just the opposite,
我不是抱怨;恰好相反,我是来表扬的.我们的报童是我们有过的最好的报童.
kudos.Our paper boy is the best paper boy we've ever had.
他是迈克尔亚伦西维尔.事实上,
His name is Michael Aaron Seaver.
因为我们对他的表现太满意了,所以,我们打算再多订一份.
In fact, we're so thrilled with him, we're gonna take another subscription.
我的名字?不能告诉你.
My name?I can't tell you.
杰森∶你看看这份报纸.叠的多好,
Jason: Will you look at this newspaper.
我敢肯定里面都是好新闻.
Perfectly folded, and I bet it's full of nothing but good news.
麦琪∶本,兴许你可以学习你的哥哥,
Maggie: Ben, maybe you can learn from your brother's example and get a
当你长大后,也可以找份报童的工作做做.
paper route when you're old enough.
本∶我要走了.
Ben: I gotta go.
麦琪∶哦!但是你才吃了8根香肠.
Maggie: Oh, but you only had eight sausages.
本∶我要点到学校,因为我今天有个补充测试!
Ben: I gotta get to school early, I got a make-up test!
杰森∶再见本.
Jason: See you Ben.
麦琪∶把体育版给我看看.10分钟后见.
Maggie: Give me the sport's section.See you in ten minutes.
杰森∶你好!我是想表扬一下你们的新的报童.
Jason: Hello.Yes I would like to compliment you on your new delivery boy.
迈克尔西维尔,对!
Michael Seaver, yes!Oh if we had them this good in East Berlin we never
如果我们在东柏林也有这么好的报童的话,那我们肯定可以做的很好!
would have left!
本∶对不起我来迟了迈克.
Ben: Sorry I'm late Mike.
迈克∶本,
Mike: Benny look, if you're not serious about this job,
听着,如果你对这个工作不是认真的,
I want you to come out and tell me right now;
我希望你马上告诉我;因为我把我一半的报酬给你的原因是...
because the only reason I'm giving you half of my paper route is because...
我应该只说...我们是一家人.
heck, I'll just say it...we're family.
还有大把人等着做这份工作呢.
And there are plenty of people who'd do this for half the money.
本∶我知道,我是说,我听到了.
Ben: I know.I mean, I've heard.
迈克∶那好,这是你的报纸.
Mike: Yeah, well!There are your papers.
记住,你一天争25美元,因此不要让我失望.
Remember, you're making twenty five Dollars a day, Ben, so don't let me down.
本∶你了解我的,迈克.
Ben: You know me, Mike.
迈克∶没错.
Mike: Yeah.
本∶加里, 你迟到了!
Ben: Gary, you're late!
加里∶没有,正好准时.
Gary: No, I'm not.Right on time.
本∶哦!哦!那是我了.
Ben: Oh, right, that was me.
托尼∶哈?
Gary: Ha?
本∶这是你的报纸,记住,如果你开始感到疲倦,
Ben: There are your papers, and remember, if you start getting tired,
只要不断的对自己说,一天10元!一天10元!
just keeping thinking to yourself, ten Bucks a day!Ten Bucks a day!
加里∶明白.
Gary: Got it.
本∶你最好开始加里.
Ben: You better get started Gary.
加里∶嗨!你走路的姿势好了很多.
Gary: Hey, you're walking better.
本∶比?哦!哦!我改穿拳击运动员短裤了.
Ben: Than what?Oh, oh, well, right, I switched to boxer shorts.
加里∶等一下!这是工作!
Gary: Wait a minute!This is work!
迈克∶你好菲莉?
Mike: How are you Philly?
菲莉∶失望的.
Philly: Despondent.
托尼∶哼!?
Mike: Huh?
菲莉∶对你的工作表现失望...
Philly: Over your performance...or the lack of there in of.
迈克∶等等,我不明白...
Mike: Wait, I still don't...
菲莉∶迈克尔.42份报纸不投递,
Philly: Michael.While not delivering forty two papers may seem like a
已经不是小小的犯罪了,假设我和你,
small transgression, let us suppose, you and I that one of your subscribers,
是其中的一个订阅者,你不要否则,
thus denied, is a man this close to solving the essential questions which
作为男人,我们必须好好的实质性的解决问题.
we wrestle with as enlightened beings.
迈克∶什么42份报纸?
Mike: What forty two papers?
菲莉∶你拿不到这42份的报酬.
Philly: The one's for which you will not receive remuneration.
迈克∶等等,等等,你能不能说英语?
Mike: Wait, wait a minute!Would you talk English?
菲莉∶好.你扔掉了42份报纸,因此,
Philly: Sure.You throw away forty two papers, you lose money.
你拿不到报酬.如果再做一次,你就失去工作!
Do it again, you lose your job!
迈克∶本,我们必须谈谈.
Mike: Benny, we must talk!
本∶我必须咀嚼.
Ben: I must chew.
迈克∶我是认真的,本.
Mike: I'm serious Benny.I just got reamed out there!
我太震惊了!昨天42个人没有得到他们的报纸!
Forty two people did not get their papers yesterday!
本∶真地?
Ben: Really?
迈克∶是,你让我失望!
Mike: Yes, but you let me down!
本∶你怎么知道是来自我的半个区域?
Ben: Well, how do you know they came from my half of the route?
迈克∶你的一半?本,
Mike: Your half?Benny,
抱怨都是来自你的半个路线!
there's only been complaints from your half of the route!
本,我每天给你50美金是干什么的?
Benny look, what am I paying you fifty Dollars a day for?
本∶你没有,你每天付给我25美金.
Ben: You're not, you're paying me twenty five.
迈克∶就是.本,
Mike: Exactly.Benny, don't lie to me!
不要骗我!你没有投递那些报纸,
You did not deliver those papers, did you?
对吗?所以我也不会付你这些报纸的报酬!
And I'm not gonna remunerate you for 'em!
本∶哈?
Ben: Ha?
迈克∶如果它再次发生,我不得不让你离开!
Mike: Look, if it happens again, I'm gonna have to let you go!
本∶你是说我再也不是你的弟弟了!
Ben: You mean I'm not gonna be your brother any more!
加里∶今天应该不会有人抱怨没有收到报纸了.
Gary: I don't think there'll be any complaints about undelivered papers today.
本∶最好,否则我得自己来了,
Ben: There better not be or I might have to step in;
无论我的胯部怎么样.
no matter what state my crotch is in.
加里∶嗨!不必担心,只要好好休息就会好的.
Gary: Hey, don't worry, man.Just rest and heal.
本∶嗨!臭虫怎么了 ?
Ben: Hey Stinky.What's the matter?
臭虫∶没事,我不能跟你说.
Stinky: Nothing's the matter, and I can't tell you what it is.
本∶臭虫,臭虫,
Ben: Stink, Stink, Stink, you'll feel better if you just let it out.
臭虫,说出来会好受点.只是表达一下你自己而已.
That's just an expression!
臭虫∶我让加里失望了.
Stinky: I let Gary down.
本∶怎样地?
Ben: How?
臭虫:我帮他送报纸,
Stinky: I was helping him out by delivering his newspapers,
每天一美元.
for a Dollar a day.
本∶一美元!!!
Ben: A Dollar!!!
臭虫∶他应该告诉他们必须全部在同一天投递.
Stinky: Wish he'd told me they all had to be delivered in the same day.
加里∶嗨!臭虫.
Gary: Hey Stinky.
本:你只给他一美元,而把剩下的二十四美元都收下了?
Ben: You've been paying him a Dollar and keeping the other twenty four?!?
加里∶24?你才给我10块!
Gary: Twenty four?You only paid me ten!
臭虫∶10块?
Stinky: Ten?!
加里∶你拿25?
Gary: You get twenty five?
本∶不要改变话题!你居然从小家伙身上赚钱.
Ben: Don't change the subject!You've making money off the little chump.
杰森∶对!
Stinky: Yeah!
加里∶你呢,你还不是一样从我身上赚钱,不是吗?
Gary: Well, what about you?You've been making money off me, right?
本∶对,只有一点,
Ben: OK, well maybe just a little but I could have skipped you and gone
我应该跳过你直接和这个笨蛋做生意,那样我就可以赚24块了!
right to the chump and made twenty four big ones!
麦琪∶宝贝儿,你在家里干什么?
Maggie: Honey, what are you doing home?
杰森∶是时候告诉你真象了,麦琪;我的新办公室是假的.每天早上我穿好衣服,然后就去藏在车库里,等到下班时间.
Jason: Well, it's time I told you the truth, Maggie; my new office was a
lie.Every morning I get all dressed up and I go hide in the garage
and wait until quitting time
麦琪∶啊哈?
Maggie: Aha?
杰森∶呵呵,开玩笑.事实是我搞糟并且处理了我4点钟的病人.
Jason: Ah, no, to tell you the truth I messed up and cured my four o' clock.
麦琪∶恩.
Maggie: Mmm.
杰森∶也不完全对.他和以前一样没什么进展.
Jason: Not really.He was as sick as ever.
不得不取消,因此,我觉得我应该早点回家,
No, I just had some cancellations so I thought I'd come home and we could
这样,我们就有点单独的时间了.
have a little quality time.
麦琪∶这个不是重点,对吗?本,出了什么事 ?
Maggie: This isn't part of it, is it?Ben, what happened?
本∶我午餐吃坏了肚子.
Ben: Errm...I had a sloppy lunch.
杰森∶站住!
Jason: Hold it!
麦琪∶苏利纨夫妇..
Maggie: Mr.and Mrs.Sullivan...
臭虫的妈妈∶西维尔夫人我们有一个问题..
Stinky's Mom: Mrs.Seaver we have a problem...
臭虫∶我没有告发你,本,他们发现了在我的内衣里的凉拌卷心菜.
Stinky: I didn't fink on you, Ben, they found coleslaw in my underwear.
臭虫的爸爸∶伯纳德,你妈妈正在说话!
Stinky's Dad: Bernard, your mother's talking!
杰森∶苏利纨夫人,发生了什么事..
Jason: Mrs.Sullivan, what happened...
臭虫的妈妈∶因为本,我们的小男孩被利用了.
Stinky's mom: Because of Ben, our little boy was taken advantage of.
麦琪∶被利用?
Maggie: Taken advantage of?
臭虫的爸爸∶还用布丁遮盖住!
Stinky's dad: And covered in pudding!
臭虫的妈妈∶都是因为本的报纸路线.
Stinky's mom: All because of Ben's paper route.
杰森∶不可能!本没有报纸路线!
Jason: Impossible!Ben doesn't even have a paper route!
迈克∶嗨!妈妈,什么时候吃晚餐?
Mike: Hey Mom, when's dinner?
杰森∶迈克有报纸路线.
Jason: Mike has a paper route.
迈克∶没关系.
Mike: Never mind.
麦琪∶站住.
Maggie: Stick around.
臭虫的爸爸∶我知道的是,我儿子每天送200份报纸,
Stinky's dad: All I know is,
只赚1美元!
my son delivered two hundred papers for a Dollar a day!
迈克:一美元!我想确信我没有听错.
Mike: A Dollar!I was just making sure that I heard that right.
臭虫的爸爸∶而本呢,什么都不做却可以白赚要么9美元,
Stinky's dad: While Ben was keeping either nine Dollars,
要么24美元!
or twenty four Dollars for doing nothing!
杰森∶迈克,到底怎么回事?
Jason: What's going on here, Mike?
迈克∶你在问本吧,爸爸?
Mike: Ah...don't you mean, Ben, Dad?
杰森∶不, 我问你,迈克!
Jason: No, I mean, Mike!
迈克∶好吧.本...
Mike: Ok, alright, Ben...err...Benny I can't cover for you any more, man!
本,我不能再替你隐瞒了!
Alright, I let Ben in for half my paper route, to help him out!
对,我让本帮我递送一半的报纸,来帮他解决困境!
But little did I know that he would use my generosity to err...
但是,我从来不知道他居然会利用我的慷慨来剥削他的小朋友.
hustle his little friend.
本∶我没有剥削臭虫,我剥削的是加里!
Ben: I didn't hustle Stinky, I hustled Gary!
麦琪∶加里是谁?
Maggie: Who's Gary?
臭虫∶就是剥削我的人.
Stinky: The kid I nailed with a pasta Vazul.
杰森∶好吧本,我们现在要知道整件事情!
Jason: Alright Ben, we want the whole story, now!
开萝尔∶喂!我又打扰大家吗?
Carol: Hi!Am I interrupting something?
迈克∶对,开萝尔!说实在的,我们对本感到失望.
Mike: Yes, you are Carol!And frankly, we're very disappointed in Ben.
麦琪∶本,我们在等着.
Maggie: Ben, we're waiting.
本∶好吧,迈克给了我他一半的报纸路线,
Ben: Well, Mike did give me half his paper route,
但是我不能处理200份报纸.
but I couldn't handle two hundred papers.
开萝尔∶我认为200份是你整个的路线吧!
Carol: I thought two hundred papers was your whole route!
本∶什么?迈克,
Ben: What?Mike, if I was delivering your whole route,
如果我要投递全部的路线,我为什么只有25元?
how come I was only getting paid twenty five Dollars?
开萝尔:你的报酬是50美元!
Carol: I thought you were getting fifty!
迈克∶50,25,你知道我数学不好的.但是这不是问题关键,本,你现在已经惹了大麻烦了.
Mike: Err...Fifty, twenty five, you know me with math.But isn't the point here
that Benny here was in deep deep trouble
麦琪∶我们会问清楚的.
Maggie: We'll see.Mr.and Mrs.
苏利纨夫妇,感谢你们让我们知道这件事情,
Sullivan, thank you for bringing this to our attention,
我们会好好的处理的.
I think we can handle it from here.
臭虫的妈妈∶我当然希望如此.我们走,伯纳德!沃尔多!
Stinky's mom: Well, I certainly hope so.Let's go Bernard!Waldo!
本∶迈克,你在剥削我!
Ben: Mike, you were holding out on me!
杰森∶如同你剥削你的朋友一样.
Jason: Like you were doing to your friends.
本∶正确地!
Ben: Exactly!
迈克∶作为其中之一,
Mike: Ah, well, look;
我认为我们全部不必再烦恼了.
I for one think that we are all getting a little upset about nothing.
杰森∶什么也没有!!迈克,你是这个金字塔计划的罪魁祸首.
Jason: Nothing!!??Mike, you're on top of a pyramid scheme here.
(电话响起)
(Phone rings)
开萝尔∶我去接,很可能是警察.
Carol: I'll get it, it's probably the police.
迈克∶爸爸,长岛预报也在赚钱呀!
Mike: Dad, look, the Long Island Herald is keeping some money too!
这就是他们的工作方式.
I mean, that's the way it's supposed to work.
麦琪∶迈克!
Maggie: Mike!
迈克∶妈妈,我们谈论的是自由企业制度,
Mike: Mom, we are talking about the free enterprise system, OK?
不是吗?也就是说,
I mean, I sold something, I kept a little profit for myself; I mean,
我销售东西,我会自己保存一点利润;难道这有错吗?
is that wrong?Mom, I should be praised, not punished!
妈妈,我应该得到赞美,
I mean, I be Lee Iacocca's parents don't ground him every time he moves
而不是惩罚!李Iacocca的父母不会因为他发展克莱斯勒公司而责备他.
a Chrysler.
杰森∶迈克!
Jason: Mike!
迈克∶爸爸,如果你想的话,
Mike: Dad, Dad, look, punish me if you want to,
那你就惩罚我吧,
but all I did was participate in a system that makes me...
但是我所做的一切让我觉得作为一个美国人,我很自豪.
heck I'll just say it...darn proud to be an American.
开萝尔∶是加里的父母打来的.
Carol: It's Gary's parents on the phone.
他们想要跟你们谈谈本的胯部治疗.
They wanna talk to you as soon as Ben's crotch heals.
开萝尔:这是迈克做的?他以后要执行自己的报纸路线.
Carol: That's all Mike got?He has to do his own paper route from now on!
杰森∶这是对他的惩罚.
Jason: That's all he got.
开萝尔∶正义到哪里去了?公平到哪里去了?
Carol: What happened to justice?What happened to equity?
我的严厉的,不宽恕的,小气的父母去哪里了?
What happened to my punishing, vindictive, petty parents?
麦琪∶哦!我们仍然在这里.
Maggie: Oh, we're still here.
迈克∶好吧!出发!不,不,不!爸爸,我的车不动了,我可以借你的车来装我的报纸吗?我会在你出发去工作前回来.
Mike: Alright.Arrgghh!Come on!No, no, no!Dad, my car won't start, can I borrow yours to take my papers.I mean, I'll have 'em back before you have to leave for work.
杰森:当然可以,迈克.
Jason: Yeah, sure Mike.
迈克∶谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
开萝尔∶哈!
Carol: Ha!
杰森∶要100美元哦.
Jason: Hundred Dollars.
迈克∶什么?
Mike: What?
杰森∶车的租金.
Jason: Car rental.
迈克∶爸爸,我一天才挣50美元.
Mike: Dad, I only make fifty Dollars a day.
杰森∶迈克,
Jason: Mike, come on,
这可是你昨天说的那么好的自由企业制度哦.
it's that free enterprise thing that you explained so well yesterday.
迈克∶爸爸,我们是一家人.
Mike: Dad, we're family.
杰森∶但是首先,我们是美国人.
Jason: But first, we're Americans.
迈克∶妈妈,我可以借你的汽车吗?
Mike: Mom, can I borrow your car?
麦琪∶当然.
Maggie: Sure.
迈克∶谢谢妈咪.
Mike: Thank you Mommy.
麦琪∶我可以用这钱.
Maggie: I could use the money.
迈克∶什么?
Mike: What?
麦琪∶200美元.我的车可是货车.
Maggie: Two hundred Dollars.It's a station wagon.
迈克∶你们是怎么了 ?
Mike: What is it with you people?
Maggie: Hey!I be Lee Iyococo's parents don't give him an attitude when
如果他做出这样的事情的话.
he does this.
迈克∶好了,我明白了.我获得了教训.
Mike: OK, OK, you guys got me.I learned my lesson.
杰森∶太棒了,迈克.
Jason: That's great, Mike.
迈克∶爸爸,我很自私吗?
Mike: Boy, Dad, was I selfish?
麦琪∶是你自己说的.
Maggie: You said it.
迈克∶妈妈,感谢给我指路.
Mike: Mom, thanks for showing me the way.
杰森∶随时乐意.
Jason: Any time.
迈克∶你们最伟大.
Mike: You guys are really the greatest.
麦琪∶迈克...
Maggie: Mike...
迈克∶是,妈妈.
Mike: Yeah, Mom.
麦琪∶你说这些还是不能减低你的租车费.
Maggie: It's still gonna cost you dearly for our cars.
杰森:麦琪你知道么,
Jason: You know Maggie,
也许我应该跟那个孩子分担.
maybe I just should of sold the kid his distributor wire.
麦琪∶还有他的火花塞.
Maggie: Or his spark plugs.
开萝尔∶我明白了;你们仍然是我的严厉的不宽恕的和小气的父母.
Carol: I take it all back; you guys are just as punishing,
vindictive and petty as you've always been.
臭虫∶本,你干什么...
Stinky: Ben, what are you doing...
本∶这是我赚的钱,我把它全部给你.
Ben: Here's the money I made, and it's all going to you.
臭虫∶哇.
Stinky: Wow.
本∶我希望你不会恨我,就算你像对傻瓜那样来对我,
Ben: I hope you don't hate me even though you treated me like a chump,
我们仍然是朋友.
and we're still friends.
臭虫∶听到这些我真的很开心.
Stinky: That's a very nice thing to say.
本∶告诉我的爸爸,是他写的.
Ben: Tell my Dad, he wrote it.
臭虫∶哇!谁会想到,
Stinky: Wow!Who knew when I started delivering papers for a Dollar a day,
居然从一天1美元投递报纸的工作开始做起,也可以变成有钱人?
I'd end up a rich man?
本∶不是我,臭虫,不是我.
Ben: Not me, Stink, not me.
臭虫∶谢谢本,你可以把我当傻瓜一样对待,任何时候都可以.迈克∶住口,
Stinky: Thanks Ben, you can treat me like a chump, any day.
本,住口!00:21:40,500
Mike: Shut up Ben, just shut up!